Dharmendra Puri

0452 629 425 | dharmendrapuri250@gmail.com.au | in | 😯

SUMMARY

Having serviced the Prince of Qatar, top-tier celebrities, and the New Zealand cricket team at a 5-start Sydney hotel, I've come to enjoy building relationships with people from diverse backgrounds and pride myself in impeccable end-to-end customer service. Complementing this is a Master's in Information Technology and Hotel Management which has provided me with strong SQL, R-coding, Php, HTML, CSS, advanced Excel, Tableau, and management skills. Having 5 years of professional experience in hospitality and administration I have also become a highly organised problem solver. Now, as a Freelance Data Analyst, I value helping businesses to convert their raw data into meaningful insights for better decisions.

KEY SKILLS

- **Data Analytics** Extracted, transferred, and loaded data with SQL, advanced Excel, R & Tableau to analyse coffee shop data set and forecast annual revenues by product.
- Data Mining Frequent Pattern Mining: Applied association rule mining, classification and clustering methods on the Mushroom and groceries data sets in University projects.
- Management/Problem Solving Managed more than 50 events for high profile companies to provide a smooth running of conferences, meetings, and gala dinners. Increased customer satisfaction rate by 10%, and revenue by 15%.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Data Analyst, Upwork

2020 – Present

- Created relational databases, schemas, and tables and loaded into SQL server for clients
- Built custom interactive visualization report from the given data set with the help of Tableau, R, & Excel
- Conducted statistical analysis such as descriptive analysis, predictive analysis, and prescriptive analysis

Guest Service Agent, Fraser Suites Sydney

2018 - 2020

- Created, updated, and modified reservations in hotel's database
- Produced reports related to daily/monthly sales and reservations.

Conference Coordinator, Hilton Sydney

2016 - 2018

- Conducted 100+ successful events with the high customer satisfaction rate
- Liaised between conference organisers, managers, sales team, and food & beverage departments to run the smooth event.

Admin Support, London College Of Commerce

2013 - 2015

- Being a part of newly opened college, conducted a student onboarding program for over 500 students for different intakes.
- Communicated with lecturers, students, and other staff to provide efficient admin support

EDUCATION

Master of Applied Information Technology, Victoria University2018 – 2020Master of International Hotel Management, BMIHMS at Torrens University2016 – 2018

Websites / Projects / Social Media



Certification

Tableau Desktop Specialist Microsoft Azure Data Fundamental Volunteers	2020 Coming Soon
USAID Student Mentor, London College of Commerce	2015-2016 2012-2013

Reference

Referees will be provided on request

Thank you for considering my application. I would love to discuss this opportunity with you and am excited to hear back.